(Penny:)Okay, I get it, I get It.
You are an emotionless robot.
(Sheldon:)Well, I try.
(Penny:)All right, let's just get
this stupid game over with.
(Sheldon:)-Great. I'll go first.
-Okay.
(Sheldon:)By the way, how are you with zippers?
(Penny:)- Why?
-Well, I really need
(Sheldon:)to go to the bathroom,
and this one's gone all cattywampus.
(Raj:)Wow, your work on jellyfish
neural nets sounds so interesting.
(Girl:)It is. You can download my paper
off the university server.
(Raj:)I will. You can download my paper
on the Van Allen Belts
(Raj:)-from the university server as well.
-I will.
(Penny:)All right.
(Howard:)How'd it go?
(Raj:)Well, if you like dry,
factual statements
(Raj:)interspersed with painful moments
of silence, it was bananas.